# **Maximiliano Andrade**

Comodoro Rivadavia - Chubut, Argentina (+54) 9 2974290031 maxiandrade62@gmail.com Linkedin-Github-Portfolio

Full Stack Developer with experience in technologies such as JavaScript, React, Redux, NodeJS, ExpressJS, PostgreSQL, Git, among others. I have specialized in both Front-end and Back-end development, creating products in agile environments. This has allowed me to strengthen skills such as collaborative work, problem-solving, and effective communication.

### **EXPERIENCE:**

#### Al Training - Scale Al

jan. 2024 - jun. 2024

#### Tasks to be performed:

- Utilize skills in React, JavaScript, and other technologies to train artificial intelligence systems.
- Correct errors, debug code and enhance the efficiency of the AI system to ensure its quality and accuracy
- · Contribute to ensuring the quality and accuracy of AI training to enhance the end-user experience.

### Full Stack Web Developer - EngPartner

nov. 2023 - dic. 2023

Academic Experience. Henry Bootcamp

Project description: A multilingual chat platform connecting people worldwide.

- Offers automatic translation, free chat, and premium feature unlocking via payments.
- Includes an admin panel for user and report management.
- Utilizes React, Redux, Node.js, Express.js, and Firebase.

## **Full Stack Teaching Assistant**

oct. 2023 - dic. 2023

Academic Experience. Henry Bootcamp

Main tasks:

- Coordinate a group of new joining students throughout the whole bootcamp experience
- Guide students in the first steps of the course and clarify their doubts
- Provide assistance in solving exercises and encourage group teamwork (Pair Programming).
- Suggest ideas to improve the Bootcamp processes.
- Promote collaboration and build community within the students

Technologies:

Languages: Javascript

Front: React, Redux, Tailwind Css.

Back: Node.js, Express.js.

Databases: PostgreSql, Firebase.

Tools: Git, Slack. Agile: Scrum.

### **BASIC EDUCATION**

• Computer Technician. Ciudad del Petróleo Technical High School. 2019.

#### PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION

• Full Stack Web Developer. Henry Bootcamp. 800 hours of theoretical and practical coursework. 2023.

# **COMPLEMENTARY EDUCATION**

- JavaScript from 0 to Details. Udemy. 2023.
- React from 0 to Expert. Udemy. 2023.

# **LANGUAGES**

Inglés C1 - Advanced.